威尔 · 森塔斯: 所以它屈服了，但是
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And
so it cave whereas but
当他得到返回的函数增量计数器定义
when he got returned up the function
increment counters definition
从运行中返回到我的新功能，并带来了它。
got returned out of the running into
my new function and brought with it.
它周围的所有本地数据都附加到函数定义上。
All its surrounding local data
attached onto the function definition.
我们马上就会知道这是怎么回事了。
We'll see all about how
this works in a moment.
现在，这里有一个美丽的小有它是一个美丽的
For now, here's a beautiful
little there it is a beautiful
背包的数据，这里就是,
backpack of data such that here it is,
当我运行我的新函数之前
such that when I run
my new function before
我全面调查了全球。
I look into global in full.
你认为我们调查的马克在哪里？
Where do you think Mark
that we look into the?
马克: 背包 威尔 · 森特斯: 放进背包,
&gt;&gt; Mark: Backpack.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Into the backpack,
作者: Mark。
spot on by Mark.
威尔 · 森特斯: 我们走进背包，发现了什么，凯拉？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Into the backpack we go,
where what do we find, Kayla?
计数器是零。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: The counter is zero.
威尔 · 森特斯: 那我们该怎么处理它呢？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And what do we do to it?
我们增加它。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: We increment it.
威尔 · 森特斯: 我们把它增加到1，她说对了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We increment it to one,
she's spot on.
她确实是
She was so
完全正确，我们必须删掉之前的部分，因为她泄露了游戏。
spot on, we have to cut the earlier
bit because she gave away the game.
让我们继续奔跑。
And let's keep running.
我们继续跑吧。
Let's keep running.
我们稍后会进一步讨论这个问题，但是我们先不谈这个执行上下文。
We'll talk more about it in a moment but
let's get out of this execution context.
顺便说一下，如果本地内存中有任何东西，它就会被删除。
By the way, if there had been anything in
local memory, it would've been deleted.
我有种感觉这些数据附加在函数定义上,
I have a feeling this data over here
attached to the function definition,
那东西哪儿也去不了。
that ain't going anywhere.
这是函数定义的一部分，不会有任何改变。
That stuck on the function definition,
that ain't going anywhere.
让我们继续运行，出来我们进入我的新函数，我们从调用堆栈中弹出它。
Let's keep running, out we come in my new
function, we pop it off the call stack.
实际上我必须这么做即使我们要再来一遍
I'm actually gonna have to, even though
we're gonna run it again just so
我们不认为这是一回事,
that we don't think it's the same,
我将从调用堆栈中取出它，然后再次添加它。
I'm literally gonna take it off
the call stack and add it again.
就是这个。
There it is.
返回到全局，在那里我们点击调用什么函数。
Go back out to global where
we hit calling what function.
我该找谁呢，丹。
Who should I call on, Dan.
丹，当我们点击调用时，什么函数？
Dan, when we hit calling, what function?
丹: 我的新功能。
&gt;&gt; Dan: MyNewfunction.
我的新功能。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: MyNewfunction.
全新的什么丹？
Brand new what Dan?
布兰: 执行环境。
&gt;&gt; Bran: Execution context.
句子: 执行上下文，很酷的堆栈，那，发生了什么，丹？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Execution context,
cool stack, that, what happens, Dan?
丹: 我的新功能已经启动了。
&gt;&gt; Dan: MyNewfunction is pushed on.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 继续，说得很好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Pushed on,
very nicely put.
让我们为 MyNewfunction 创建执行上下文。
Let's create that execution context for
MyNewfunction.
我们走进去，本地记忆里没有任何声明。
Into it we go,
nothing in the local memory declared.
我们要运行的代码是什么，托德？
And what is our line of
code we got to run, Todd?
托德: 柜台柱子。
&gt;&gt; Todd: Counter post post.
威尔 · 森特斯: 说得好，托德，太棒了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Well on Todd, excellent.
托德，我们先去哪里找柜台？
Where Todd do we look for counter first?
托德: 在当地的记忆里。
&gt;&gt; Todd: In the local memory.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 在当地的记忆里。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: In the local memory.
我们能找到柜台吗？
Do we find counter?
托德: 没有 威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们不知道。
&gt;&gt; Todd: No.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We don't.
陶德，我们接下来去哪里？
Todd, where do we go and look out to next?
托德: 背包 威尔 · 森特斯: 放进背包,
&gt;&gt; Todd: Backpack.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Into the backpack,
他说对了。
he's spot on.
我们来看看 myNewFunction 的定义,
We go look at myNewFunction's definition,
我们看看它和永久储存的数据，背包之间的联系。
we look at the little connection to its
permanent stored data, the backpack.
然后我们就去了。
And off we go to it.
托德: (笑)威尔 · 森塔斯: 就是这样，而且
&gt;&gt; Todd: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: There it is and
进去吧。
in we go.
我们过去常常这样，我们去，它是一，我们做什么？
We used to be that bit up in the and in we
go and it's one and we do what with it?
我们把它增加到，看看那个人。
We increment it to, to look at that folk.
第一次，我们的函数 myNewFunction,
For the very first time,
our function myNewFunction,
一个函数定义不只是有它的本地内存，逐字逐句地得到我应该
a function definition doesn't just have it
local memory that gets literally I should
真的做到了这一点，真的做到了，每次都被删除。
have actually done this,
literally gets right, deleted each time.
我们现在不仅有暂时的局部记忆,
We now have not only
the temporary local memory,
如果我们不把存储全球的东西还回去，它就永远消失了。
that if we don't return something out
in storing global, it's gone forever.
我们也有一个非常明确的定义,
We also have the very
definition the label,
功能存储器附加了一个永久存储器。
the function storage has attached
to it a permanent memory.
这真是不可思议。
That is remarkable.
也就是说，这个标签不再只是一个函数的代码保存,
That is a say no longer is this a label
for just a function from code saved,
这是关闭基金的标签，还有一些永久存储的数据。
it's a label for funds in closing and
some permanent store data attached.
真的非常非常，这是所有 JavaScript 中最优雅的特性。
Genuinely very very, this is the most
elegant feature of all of JavaScript.
优雅的意思是，我知道那是什么意思，有点像有趣的,
Elegant meaning like, I know what that
means it was sort of like interesting,
有趣而且令人惊讶的，精心制作的功能。
intriguing and surprisingly
kind of nicely crafted feature.
这就是我所说的优雅。
And that's what I mean by elegant.
我喜欢用这个词,
I like using that word,
人们不知道自己在说什么的时候，就会这么说。
that's one of those words people use
when they don't know what they mean.
掩饰自己不知道它们的意思。
To mask not knowing what they mean.
他们不知道为什么他们认为这是好的，他们觉得这是优雅的。
They're not sure why they think it's good,
and they're like that's elegant.
那么，让我们开始讨论一些注意事项,
So, let's start talking about
some caveats around this,
包括我们称之为。
including what do we call this.
首先我想说的是，函数是如何抓取的
The first bit I want to talk about though
is, how does the function get to grab
然后用函数定义返回？
onto what it surrounding data and return
it out with the function definition?
这是什么？
What is like this?
一旦，我甚至没有足够的空间来容纳这个，但是
As soon as,
I never quite even have room for this, but
一旦我们声明增量计数器。
as soon as we declare increment counter.
这实际上是存储在计算机的内存中，存储在计算机存储中
That is literally saving in the computer's
memory, in the computer store
函数和数据，一个标签，还有函数的代码。
of functions and data, a label, and
the code of the function kinda plus plus.
这就是现在的情况。
That's what this is here.
在引擎盖下，如果您有一个控制台日志，将看到函数定义。
Under the hood, if you had a console log
that would see the function definition.
根据控制台的复杂程度，我们可以看到它的整个代码，或者
Depending on how sophisticated a console
is, we'd see the whole code of it, or
在更传统的控制台上，你可能会看到类似的功能。
in more traditional console,
you'd might see like function.
在后台，在 JavaScript 中，会立即得到一个隐藏属性。
That behind the scenes, in JavaScript,
immediately gets a hidden property.
当它们有小方括号时，你总是知道它们是隐藏属性
You always know they're hidden properties
when they have little square brackets
之前和之后，在规范中，在 JavaScript 的规则中。
before and after them, in the spec,
in the rules of JavaScript.
它得到一个隐藏属性，方括号，方括号,
It gets a hidden property,
square bracket, square bracket,
也就是说这里有隐藏的财产。
that means there's a hidden property.
范围方括号方括号,
Scope, square bracket, square bracket,
它是一个隐藏属性，链接到所有周围数据存储的地方。
it is a hidden property that links to
where all this surrounding data is stored.
它提供了一个与周围所有数据的链接。
It gives a little link to
all that surrounding data.
意思是当我返回那个函数时，增量计数器
Meaning when I return that function out,
increment counter
我的新功能，你打赌它带来了它的隐藏属性和
out of out of into my NewFunction,
you bet it brings it's hidden property and
通过隐藏的方括号获取数据,
pulls that data with it through
its hidden square bracket,
方括号，范围，性质。
square bracket, scope, property.
当我们给这个函数贴上新的全局标签时，它还是附着着的,
It's still attached when we give
that function its new global label,
我的新功能。
my new function.
当我运行在本地内存计数器中找不到的新函数时,
And when I run my new function I don't
find in the local memory counter,
算是介入吧。
it kind of intercedes.
在我们去环球旅行之前，它被困在了路上，因为环球旅行会先检查我们的背包。
It gets stuck in the way before we go out
to global, which first check the backpack.
这就是我们看到我们的计数器存放的地方，它不会去任何地方。
And that's where we see our counter is
stored and it ain't going anywhere.
它不像执行上下文临时内存。
It's not like an execution
context temporary memory.
只要函数定义没有被覆盖，它就是永久的,
It's permanent as long as its function
definitions they're not overwritten,
这个一直留在那里，一直都在。
this stuck around,
is still there permanently.
但是除了运行这个函数之外，我们不能以任何其他方式访问它
We can't get access to it though in any
other way besides running this function
希望代码是这样写的，当它被定义，当它出生,
and hoping the code was written in such
a way when it was defined, when was born,
最初被保存，它寻找一些本地记忆，它不在那里。
was initially saved, that it looks for
something a local memory, it ain't there.
它指的不是局部的记忆。
It refers to something
is not a local memory.
然后它出去，并查看范围属性进入背包。
Then it goes out and looks on
the scope property into the backpack.
当我们保存这个函数的时候，有一些东西被拿出来了
And there was something from when we save
that function that's being pulled out
在背包里。
in the backpack.
我们不能这样做，这是不允许的。
We cannot do this, this is not allowed.
没有比 MyNewFunction.backpack.counter 更好的了。
There's no like
MyNewFunction.backpack.counter.
这不是说我们不能通过这种方式获得它。
That is not we can't get
access to it that way.
我们甚至不能使用我的新功能。
We can't go MyNewFunction even.scope.
这是一个隐藏属性，我们不能访问它。
This is a hidden property,
we can't access it.
它就在那里，在幕后，但我们甚至不能使用 myNewFunction.scope.counter。
It's ther, behind the scenes, but we can't
even go myNewFunction.scope.counter.
获取数据的唯一方法是运行这个函数,
The only way to get to that data
is by running this function,
在当地的记忆中，它指的是一些不存在的东西
having it refer to something not in
local memory of it, and going out to
这个函数的定义就是在它的背包里找到计数器。
the function's definition looking in
its backpack and finding counter there.
绝对是一个非常非常特别的功能。
Absolutely a very, very special feature.
我们现在有了永久的，但是顺便说一下，我们称之为私人数据。
We now have permanent, but also by
the way, let's call it private data.
除了运行我们创建的函数之外，没有其他人可以访问它
No one else can access it besides by
running the function that we created to
在我们的应用程序里找到它。
get access to it in our application.
你知道吗，事实上我现在不想再多说什么了
And you know what, I'm actually gonna save
for now any further words on this besides
说，只是想想，如果我现在有一个函数有一个永久的记忆,
to say, just be thinking, if I have a
function now that has a permanent memory,
想想我能做些什么。
think what sort of things I can do.
我不会谈论我们能做的所有事情
I won't talk about all
the things we can do, but for
只是一个提示，我可以有这个函数的第二次运行,
just a hint, I can have this
function the second time it runs,
检查如果计数器是一，假设我增加它第一次。
check if counter is one,
suppose I increment it first time.
如果柜台是一个然后返回，对不起，你不能运行我超过一次。
If counter is one then return, sorry,
you can't run me more than once.
也就是说，这个函数通过它的永久内存来记住以前的运行。
That is to say this function remembers the
previous running via its permanent memory.